Seino!
The "Gakari Channel"!
Loud!
Nice! Yeah!
Let's do it!
Today is my day on the 8th!
Today I brought a girl who wanted to know!
This is Misaki.
Yes, I'm Claire.
Yes, I'm Yuza.
You nominated me.
Yes, but, um...
She wanted to know.
Yes, maybe this time.
Oh, I'm done.
And the comment about picking him up!
As for Clear, I think it's the longest encounter with him.
And there are a lot of episodes with Kurya.
As for Yuzuha, she seemed to know the least about me.
I thought she seemed to know a lot about me, so I decided to close it.
Misaki seemed to want to join me.
Hopefulness?
Was it?
Why do you say that? I called it.
But I'm curious.
I'm looking forward to working with you.
My timeline is as follows.
Misaki asked me to write about my trip abroad.
Oh, that's right.
So, I'll talk while looking at my notes.
I'll look at my notes as I speak.
I was born on April 2, 2004.
I was supposed to be born on the 1st, but I'm going to try the 2nd.
Thank you for watching.
I think the first two days were good for him, and he's going to give me that challenge! He's a strong mommy genius, and he went to Australia when he was 2 years old, so he's a big boy!
In 2007, when he was 3 years old, he started kindergarten, but he was the first baby to enter kindergarten.
He was the first baby, so he only had contact with his mother, father, and grandmother.
I was not yet a baby, and I didn't have a younger sister at that time.
I didn't have a sister at that time... so I started going to the school, but I didn't know how to shake hands with other strangers.
I was like, "I'm going to take her there for one more day, and if she cries a lot after that, I'm going to give her a hard time.
But after that one day, he finally became happy and went through to the end.
I'm sure you'll be in Singapore in the winter with the ultimate person from the second ultimate.
The number of extracurricular trips is very high.
By the way, do you speak English all the time at the international school?
Yes, so it's English all the time, but if I speak Japanese they make me sit down.
I can't speak beyond that point... so I always put "rai" after the Japanese word... and he's like...
I always put "rai" after the Japanese word and then something like "right now we're playing" and then I'd say "ok".
So, in 2008...
I started going to that dance school in 2008, but then I heard there was an expd studio next to this one, so I moved here soon.
I'm 4 years old, so I've been going to expd studio since I was 4.
I'm talking about a simple trip... a simple trip... but it's like a wedding... here.
I wanted to have a wedding here, so I had my mom and dad's wedding here, just the family, and we were here for about two weeks.
I'll start skiing next time.
I moved to the board the next year when I was 5.
Yes, yes, specs.
my mom's job is to take pictures and put them up on a wall or something... and she went to take my picture for a photo shoot... and later that day... she called me... and said she was going to take my picture.
I went to have my picture taken, and later that day I got a call and became a signboard for this store.
So it's the 15th anniversary of your debut at the age of 5?
If you include this as part of my work, it's been 15 years.
You were a senior.
I was senior to everyone.
And you were committed to taking care of her.
That's right.
I went to Hawaii in October of 2006.
The next winter, when I was 11, I went to Korea with a friend's family.
I just realized... what's the number in parentheses?
What numbers are they?
Parentheses.
Here's my age.
10 years old in 2006... 8 years old... 9 years old, 10 years old, 11 years old...
So, 11 years old and back in 2006... ignore my age...
So here's 10 years old, here's 10 years old, and here's 10 years old... and here we are.
I heard about this photo studio in '13 and '14 and I took it with a friend of mine and we won the grand prize in '13 and then we won some kind of petit chocolat award and I seriously don't know where I would be in my career if I hadn't become a signboard for it. I don't know where my career would have gone if I hadn't gotten that billboard.
I've been playing piano here since I was 4 years old and quit when I was in 4th grade
I'm in the 4th grade here and I auditioned for the special student program and I got an international flight.
I auditioned for a special student program and got an international flight with Expg Expg and that's when I met Claire.
Nice to meet you, it's nice to meet you, it's nice to meet you, it's nice to meet you, it's nice to meet you, it's nice to meet you, it's nice to meet you.
I played the role of a slave in a movie set in Miyazaki, and I was in the clean view, and I thought we had a strong role together, and we were powerful, but...
I played a slave in the movie "Slave," and I was the hope of the moment.
I believe I'll never get to see him again... in the Children of Mythology.
I've done a lot of things around here... like back up dancer for Exile's live shows... but my first time was in the 4th grade.
I was in my fourth year of elementary school when I first started working as a back dancer for Exile's live shows.
I needed a notebook and a pen on the big stage.
At rehearsals.
We always needed them.
I've heard that before, right?
You told us to bring a pen and notebook.
Yes, sir.
There were only about two of us at that rehearsal.
That's right, there were only about two of us.
And every time I forget my notebook and pen.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
I hate it.
I get so mad at the end of the day, and they clear my concentration train.
In the 5th grade, I decided I wanted to do more serious work, so I quit.
So I quit, but when I was in the sixth grade, they asked me to come back.
I became a candidate for the FNS Serious Dance Championship.
I was in the FNS Serious Dance Championships... with Claire.
We had a two-person team.
From Miyazaki?
Yes, the Bumpy Mango.
I hear that a lot.
Sometimes I search for it, and it comes up. It's in Regent.
In 2016.
Oh, here.
I met Miuka and Minami... and I was working as a model at the time, so I met Minami's sister.
That's where I met Minami's sister.
Minami's sister was working as a model, and Minami came along with her, and that's how I met the little Minami.
I was 12 years old in 2016, and I was auditioning for both the summer and winter shows.
Miracle Tunes.
I was told there was one more audition, and they asked me which one I wanted to do, and I thought that one was more for overseas.
So I auditioned for that one, and at the camp, I met Yuna from Ice Cream and Norio Nijio.
I met Yuna from Ice Cream and Norio Nijio at that camp, and then I met Momoka and Kira at another camp for candidates in the winter.
I also took the junior high school entrance exam here, but in November of my sixth grade year, I decided that I wanted to go to a private junior high school, and it was just around the corner.
I told you, I've never even been to a private school.
So I decided to take the past exam and got about 20 points.
I was very scared at Ogawa Juku, and we studied together until about 2 a.m. I was doing it in the room with the Buddhist altar, and I would make him yell out, "Let's do this!
I heard that he cheered me up, and he was nodding off a lot.
I was so sick of it... but he told me to give it up... but I didn't want to.
I was told to give it up, but I didn't want to, and thanks to your help, I passed.
I started going to a private junior high school, and in the summer of 2017, there was a camp again, and I wrote an article about it.
I'm not sure if it's the same thing as the other two, but I'm not sure if it's the same thing as the other two.
And we turned it down... so maybe that's when we met Tomo... around the time of the summer camp.
So we said no and went back to our hometown.
At Miyazaki school, for some reason, we sang the song "Catch Me" and "Jump" as an assignment and made a video of it.
And later on, for some reason, I had a parent-teacher meeting and was offered a job at Maji Geopurez.
It was a little different from what I wanted to do, so I was very hesitant.
But I knew it was a chance to make my dream come true, so my father gave me a push.
I worked hard to get into a private junior high school, but I dropped out after half a year and moved to Tokyo in October.
Thank you very much for your support.
I met Misaki here.
Nice to meet you.
Yes... why are you two so great?
As for me and Clear, we've been in the same boat ever since we met.
We've been living the same kind of life since we met.
We've been living the same life ever since we met.
I'm sure you're all aware of that.
I'm sure all the fans know that.
I'm sure you know this.
I've met Yuzuha around here.
I've already met Yuzu around here.
Everyone knows.
I thought maybe that's it.
I see. Interesting. What a life!
But it's true, I'm the type of person who can't do things unless they're on the edge.
I can do it at the bottom.
You're still good, right? I'm getting carried away, but I'll be fine.
Let's just call it quits. Let's just call it quits.
Wow, that's great. Like this?
Interesting. That was Yohka Ogawa's review of her own performance.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for watching
Well, let's see.
If you enjoyed it, please give us a high rating, subscribe to our channel, and comment!
Thank you very much.
Bye bye!
This time I'm wearing Bigo's outfit